Guide to the Ronald Lawson Research Files for the Tenant Movement in New York City TAM.214
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Research Files (box 11): Tenant Association Building Leader Questionnaires
  - 28-30 34th Street Tenants Association: 28-30 34th Street, Queens: Domini Frank Bone, Emma Fayntaren, Jan 1975-Apr 10, 1976, undated (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - (Queens Tenants Federation): 40-40 Elbertson Street Tenants Association: 40-40 Elbertson Street, Elmhurst, Queens: Mr. Hilbert, Adie Varille, May 12, [1975], Apr 13, 1976, undated (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Research Files (box 12): Includes South Brooklyn Legal Service; United Riverdale Tenants Association; Astoria Tenants Council
  - Hillcrest Tenants Association of Jackson Heights: 70-35 Broadway, Jackson Heights, Queens: Louise Miele, Dorothy O'Brien, Nov 21, 1975-Apr 17, 1976, undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Residents Advisory Council: Yetta Wellins, Mar 19, 1975, undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Riverside Edgecombe Neighborhood Association: 1532 Amsterdam Avenue Tenants Organization: 1532 Amsterdam Avenue, NY: Bertha Puguese, Lilly Sauders, July 21 1975, Apr 19, 1976, undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Riverside Edgecombe Neighborhood Association: 461 West 164th Street, NY: Shirley Cerrano, Thomas Hill, Aug 1975, undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - (Riverside Edgecombe Neighborhood Association): 75 Fort Washington Tenant Committee: 75 Fort Washington Avenue: Mr and Marina Tate, Paul Bower, Jul 15, 1975, May 22, 1976, undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Bedford-Stuyvesant Restoration Corp. - Clippings, Nov 1974-Dec 1976 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Brooklyn (Bed-Stuy) Tenant Action Committee - Clippings, Aug 8, 1974-Spring 1976 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Brighton Beach Tenants Council - Fieldwork Report, Oct 2, 1973-Dec 20, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Brooklyn #5: Block Association within the Crown Heights Area - Fieldwork Report, May 9, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Brooklyn Tenants Alliance - 087and Leaders, undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Brownsville Community Council Inc. - Student Papers, May 29, 1973, undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Brownsville Community Action Corporation - Clippings, Feb 1975-Apr 1975 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Bushwick Community Corporation - Student Papers, Mar 14, 1973, May 1974, undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Bushwick-Williamburg Legal Services - Student Paper, Spring 1974 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Cornelia Tenants Housing Development Fund Company Corporation - Student Paper, undated (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Crown Heights Coalition 073 and Leaders, undated (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Crown Heights - Student Papers and Clippings, Spring 1972-Dec 1973, undated (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Fort Greene Community Corporation - Student Paper, May 29, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Methodist Hospital - 083 and Leaders, undated (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Methodist Hospital Tenants Association - Student Papers, 1972, 1973, undated (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Ocean Hill-Brownsville Tenant Association, Dec 10, 1975-Sep 25, 1980, undated (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Ocean-Kings Tenant Council - Student Papers, May 1974-Dec 1974 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Park Slope Tenants Association - Student Papers, May 29, 1973, undated (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Prospect-Lefferts Gardens Neighborhood Association Inc., Mar 1975-Oct 1976 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Park Slope Neighborhood Tenants Council Bulletin, undated (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Prospect-Lefferts Garden Neighborhood Association - Student Paper, Jan 11, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - St. Nicholas Housing Corporation - Student Papers, Fall 1976, undated (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Sheephead-Brighton Tenant Association - Student Paper, May 29, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Sheepshead Brighton Tenants Council - Student Papers, undated (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - South Brooklyn Legal Services, undated (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - South Brooklyn Legal Services Meeting Notes, Feb 26, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - South Brooklyn Legal Services Meeting Notes, Feb 26, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - South Brooklyn Legal Services - 300, Feb 26, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - South Brooklyn Legal Services - 500, Feb 26, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - South Brooklyn Legal Services - 600, undated (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - South Brooklyn Legal Services - 900, undated (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - South Brooklyn Legal Services - Extra Sheets, Feb 26, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Southside Community Mission - Student Paper, Jan 3, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Sunset Park Redevelopment Committee - Clippings, Feb 3, 1974-Aug 30, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Tri Block Crown Gardens Association, Brooklyn - Student Paper, undated (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - untitled - Student Paper (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Williamsburg Community Corporation, undated (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Bathgate Community Housing Development Corporation - Student Papers, undated (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - The Bronx Church Coalition, Dec 1973 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Bronx Community College, undated (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Bronx Council on Rents and Housing, undated (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Bronx Tenants Union, undated (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Concourse Mosholu Action Association, Jan 1975 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Hunt Point Multi-Service Center - Student Paper, May 27, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Kelly Street Block Association, Fall 1976 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - League of Autonomous Bronx Organization for Renewal, undated (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Leland House Tenants Association - Student Paper, undated (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Morris Heights Neighborhood Improvement Association - Student Papers, Jun 2, 1976, undated (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Mosholu-Woodlawn South Community Coalition, Dec 18, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - South Fordham Organization - Student Papers, Spring 1976-Jan 10, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - 104-76 Tenant Information Program, Apr 16, 1972-Dec 7, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - 104-76 Meeting Notes, Oct 26, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - 104-76 Meeting Notes, Oct 26, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - 104-76 - 089 and Leaders, Oct 30, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - 104-76 - 100, Oct 26, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - 104-76 - 200, Oct 26, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - 104-76 - 300, undated (Box 12, Folder 62)
  - 104-76 - 400, undated (Box 12, Folder 63)
  - 104-76 - 500, Oct 30, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 64)
  - 104-76 - 600, undated (Box 12, Folder 65)
  - 104-76 - 700, Oct 30, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 66)
  - 104-76 - Extra Copies and Sheets, Oct 26, 1973-Oct 30,1973 (Box 12, Folder 67)
  - Simpson Street Development Association (SISDA):, undated (Box 12, Folder 68)
  - SISDA - student papers, Jan 2, 1973, Dec 1975 (Box 12, Folder 69)
  - South Fordham Organization - student paper: Savitz, Lorraine. "The Analysis of Social Movement Theory Utilizing Data Collected from the United Farm Workers Movement, The Tenant Movement, and South Fordham Organization.", Jan 10, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 70)
  - South Bronx Action Group Inc., Mar 3, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 71)
  - South Bronx Community Housing Coroporation - Student Papers - Field Summary, undated (Box 12, Folder 72)
  - Tenants Against Union Hospital Expansion, Dec 11, 1973-Jan 6, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 73)
  - United Riverdale Tenants Association - Meeting Notes, Feb 13, 1974, Mar 20, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 74)
  - United Riverdale Tenants Association - Meeting Notes, Feb 13, 1974, Mar 20, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 75)
  - United Riverdale Tenants Association - 037 and Leaders, undated (Box 12, Folder 76)
  - United Riverdale Tenants Association - 100, Mar 20, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 77)
  - United Riverdale Tenants Association - 300, Feb 13, 1974, Mar 20, 1974, undated (Box 12, Folder 78)
  - United Riverdale Tenants Association - 400, Feb 13, 1974, Mar 20, 1974, undated (Box 12, Folder 79)
  - United Riverdale Tenants Association - 500, Feb 13, 1974, Mar 20, 1974, undated (Box 12, Folder 80)
  - United Riverdale Tenants Association - 600, Feb 13, 1974, Mar 20, 1974, undated (Box 12, Folder 81)
  - United Riverdale Tenants Association - 700, Feb 13, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 82)
  - United Riverdale Tenants Association - 800, Feb 13, 1974, Mar 20, 1974, undated (Box 12, Folder 83)
  - United Riverdale Tenants Association - 900, Feb 13, 1974, Mar 20, 1974, undated (Box 12, Folder 84)
  - Washington Heights Tenants Association - 084 and Leaders, undated (Box 12, Folder 85)
  - Wakefield Tenants Association - Student Paper, May 28, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 86)
  - West Bronx Tenant Union - publications, undated (Box 12, Folder 87)
  - West Bronx Tenants Union - Meeting Notes, undated (Box 12, Folder 88)
  - Astoria Tenants Organizating Committee, Oct 15, 1973, undated (Box 12, Folder 89)
  - Astoria Tenants Council - Meeting Notes, Oct 1, 1973, Oct 15, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 90)
  - Astoria Tenants Council, Oct 15, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 91)
  - Astoria Tenants Council - 100: Ecology, Oct, 1, 1973, Oct 15, 1973, undated (Box 12, Folder 92)
  - Astoria Tenants Council - 200: Beginnings and History, undated (Box 12, Folder 93)
  - Astoria Tenants Council - 300, undated (Box 12, Folder 94)
  - Astoria Tenants Council - 400, Oct 15, 1973, undated (Box 12, Folder 95)
  - Astoria Tenants Council - 500, Oct 1, 1973, Oct 15, 1973, undated (Box 12, Folder 96)
  - Astoria Tenants Council - 600, undated (Box 12, Folder 97)
  - Astoria Tenants Council - 700, undated (Box 12, Folder 98)
  - Astoria Tenants Council - 900, undated (Box 12, Folder 99)
  - Astoria Tenants Council - Extra Sheets and Copies, Oct 1, 1973, Oct 15, 1973, undated (Box 12, Folder 100)
- Research Files (box 13): Includes: Melrose Organization for Community Action; Bensonhurst Ten ants Council; Boro Park Tenants Council; Queens Tenant Federation; Chelsea Coalition on Housing
  - Cosmopolitan Tenant Association - student papers, Jan 3, 1973, May 23, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Flushing - Student Paper, Tenants Association of the Stanton, Greater Flushing Tenants Council, Apr 1977-Dec 1977, undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Glen Oaks Tenants Association - Student Paper, Spring 1974 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Howard-Carol Tenants Association - Student Paper, undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Pomonok Tenants Council - The Tenant, Oct 1973 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Pomonok Tenants Council - Student Papers, Jan 2, 1973, undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Rochdale Village, Mar 1974, undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Rochdale Village, Dorie Miller Cooperative - Student Papers, Clippings, Oct 23, 1973-Dec 28, 1973, undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Southeast Queens Community Corporation - Student Papers, Jan 1, 1973-May 29, 1973, undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - South Jamaica Tenant Association - Student Paper, Dec 29, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Woodside Tenants Association, undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Queensbridge-Astoria-Long Island City (Q.U.A.L.I) Corporation, undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Windsor Park Tenants Assocation - Student Papers, Nov 17, 1972, Dec 28, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Staten Island Tenant Organizations - Student Papers, Jan 2, 1973, Fall 1974, undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Melrose Organization for Community Action, undated (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Melrose Organization for Community Action - (Notes, Area Served, Interviews (Sr. Nieves, Trussell)), Sep 26, 1973, undated (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Melrose Organization for Community Action/Morrisiania Community Corporation/Council Against Poverty, Sep 4, 1973-Jan 30, 1975, undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Melrose Organization for Community Action - Student Papers, undated (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Melrose Organization for Community Action - Meeting Notes, Sep 26, 1973-Feb 14, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Melrose Organization for Community Action - Meeting Notes, Sep 26, 1973-Feb 14, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Melrose Organization for Community Action - 041 and Leaders, Sep 26, 1973, undated (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Melrose Organization for Community Action - 100: Ecology, undated (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Melrose Organization for Community Action - 200: Beginnings and History, undated (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Melrose Organization for Community Action - 300: Structure and Finances, Sep 26, 1973, Dec 7, 1973, undated (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Melrose Organization for Community Action - 400: Goals and Tactics, Dec 7, 1973, undated (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Melrose Organization for Community Action - 500: Leaders and Key Personnel, Sep 26, 1973, Oct 10, 1973, undated (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Melrose Organization for Community Action - 600: Membership and Mobilization, undated (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Melrose Organization for Community Action - 700: Observer and the Group, Sep 26, 1973, undated (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Melrose Organization for Community Action - 900: Related Institutions, undated (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Bensonhurst Tenants Council - Student Papers, Dec 3, 1973-May 21, 1974, Spring 1977 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Bensonhurst Tenants Council - 100, Feb 14, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Bensonhurst Tenants Council - 300, undated (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Bensonhurst Tenants Council - 400, Dec 3, 1973, Feb 14, 1974, undated (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Bensonhurst Tenants Council - 500, Feb 21, 1974, undated (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Bensonhurst Tenants Council - 600, Dec 3, 1973, Feb 14, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Bensonhurst Tenants Council - 700, Feb 21, 1974-May 21, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Bensonhurst Tenants Council - 800, Apr 4, 1974, undated (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Bensonhurst Tenants Council - 900, undated (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Bensonhurst Tenants Council - Monograph by K. Schneider, undated (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Bensonhurst Tenants Council - mailing, Oct 1973 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Bensonhurst Tenants Council - Student Papers, Dec 18, 1975, Fall 1976, undated (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Bensonhurst Tenants Council - Meeting Notes, Dec 3, 1973-May 22, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Bensonhurst Tenants Council - Meeting Notes, Dec 3, 1973-May 21, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Bensonhurst Tenants Council - 017 and Leaders, May 21, 1974, undated (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Boro Park Tenants Council, Sep 25, 1973-May 16, 1974, undated (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Boro Park Tenants Council - Monograph by K. Schnneider, undated (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Boro Park Tenants Council - newsletters and mailings, May 1973-May 1974, undated (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Boro Park Tenants Council - Student Papers, Jan 2, 1973, May 1974, undated (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Boro Park Tenants Council - Meeting Notes, Sep 25, 1973-May 15, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Boro Park Tenants Council - Meeting Notes, Sep 25, 1973-May 16, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Boro Park Tenants Council - 018 and Leaders, Sep 25, 1973-May 16, 19xx, undated (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - Boro Park Tenants Council - 100, Sep 25, 1973, undated (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - Boro Park Tenants Council - 200, Apr 3, 1974, May 16, 1974, undated (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - Boro Park Tenants Council - 300, Dec 1973-May 16, 1974, undated (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - Boro Park Tenants Council - 400, Oct 3, 1973-Apr 24, 1974, undated (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - Boro Park Tenants Council - 500, Oct 23, 1973-Feb 4, 1974, undated (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - Boro Park Tenants Council - 600, Dec 11, 1973, undated (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - Boro Park Tenants Council - 700, Feb 4, 1974-Feb 13, 1974, undated (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - Boro Park Tenants Council - 800, Apr 3, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 58)
  - Boro Park Tenants Council - 900, undated (Box 13, Folder 59)
  - Boro Park Tenants Council - Extra Sheets, Sep 25, 1973-May 16, 1974, undated (Box 13, Folder 60)
  - Queens Tenants Federation, Feb 7, 1974-Apr 19, 1974, undated (Box 13, Folder 61)
  - Queens Tenants Federation, undated (Box 13, Folder 62)
  - Queens Tenants Federation - Monograph by K. Schneider, undated (Box 13, Folder 63)
  - Queens Tenants Federation - Meeting Notes, Feb 20, 1974-May 13, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 64)
  - Queens Tenants Federation - Meeting Notes, Feb 7, 1974-May 13, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 65)
  - Queens Tenants Federation - 035 and Leaders, Feb 13, 1974, undated (Box 13, Folder 66)
  - Queens Tenants Federation - 100, Apr 9, 1974, undated (Box 13, Folder 67)
  - Queens Tenants Federation - 200, Feb 7, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 68)
  - Queens Tenants Federation - 300, Feb 7, 1974-Apr 9, 1974, undated (Box 13, Folder 69)
  - Queens Tenants Federation - 400, Apr 18, 1974, undated (Box 13, Folder 70)
  - Queens Tenants Federation - 500, Feb 20, 1974-May 13, 1974, undated (Box 13, Folder 71)
  - Queens Tenants Federation - 600, Feb 20, 1974, undated (Box 13, Folder 72)
  - Queens Tenants Federation - 700, Feb 7, 1974-Apr 18, 1974, undated (Box 13, Folder 73)
  - Queens Tenants Federation - 800, undated (Box 13, Folder 74)
  - Queens Tenants Federation - 900, undated (Box 13, Folder 75)
  - Queens Tenants Federation - Extra Sheets, Feb 7, 1974-May 13, 1974, undated (Box 13, Folder 76)
  - Queens Tenants Federation - Student Papers, undated (Box 13, Folder 77)
  - Chelsea Coalition on Housing, Oct 2, 1973-Jan 9, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 78)
  - Chelsea Coalition on Housing - Meeting Notes, Oct 2, 1973-Jan 9, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 79)
  - Chelsea Coalition on Housing - Mailing, undated (Box 13, Folder 80)
  - Chelsea Coalition on Housing - Meeting Notes, Oct 2, 1973-Jan 9, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 81)
  - Chelsea Coalition on Housing - 026 and Leaders, undated (Box 13, Folder 82)
  - Chelsea Coalition on Housing - 100: Ecology, Oct 2, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 83)
  - Chelsea Coalition on Housing - 200, Dec 18, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 84)
  - Chelsea Coalition on Housing - 300: Structure and Finances, undated (Box 13, Folder 85)
  - Chelsea Coalition on Housing - 400: Goals and Tactics, Dec 18, 1973, Jan 9, 1974, undated (Box 13, Folder 86)
  - Chelsea Coalition on Housing - 500: Leaders and Key Personnel, Dec 18, 1973, undated (Box 13, Folder 87)
  - Chelsea Coalition on Housing - 600: Membership, undated (Box 13, Folder 88)
  - Chelsea Coalition on Housing - 900: Related Institutions, undated (Box 13, Folder 89)
  - Chelsea Coalition on Housing - Extra Copies and Sheets, Oct 2, 1973-Jan 9, 1974, undated (Box 13, Folder 90)
  - Chelsea Coalition on Housing - Student Papers and Clippings, Nov 17, 1972-Jan 5, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 91)
  - Chelsea Tenants for Better Housing - Student Papers, undated (Box 13, Folder 92)
- Research Files (box 14): Includes Queens Presidents' Council; Parkchester Tenants Association; Riverdale Park Tenants Association; West Side Tenants Union
  - Queens Presidents' Council, Dec 4, 1973-Jun 4, 1974, undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Queens Presidents' Council - Clippings, Jan 9, 1970-May 5, 1975, undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Queens Presidents' Council - Miriam Jacobson's Notes, Oct 29, 1974-Dec 15, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Queens Presidents' Council - Meeting Notes, Dec 4, 1973-Apr 18, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Queens Presidents' Council - Meeting Notes, Dec 4, 1973-Apr 18, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Queens Presidents' Council - 013 and Leaders, Feb 19, 1974-Jun 3, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Queens Presidents' Council - 100, undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Queens Presidents' Council - 200, Dec 4, 1973, Mar 19, 1974, undated (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Queens Presidents' Council - 300: Structure and Finances, Feb 4, 1974-Apr 16, 1974, undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Queens Presidents' Council - 400: Goals and Tactics, Dec 4, 1973-Apr 18, 1974, undated (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Queens Presidents' Council - 500: Leaders and Key Personnel, Dec 4, 1973-Apr 18, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Queens Presidents' Council - 600: Membership and Mobilization, Dec 4, 1973, undated (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Queens Presidents' Council - 700: The Observer and the Group, Mar 4, 1974-Apr 17, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Queens Presidents' Council - 800: Movement and Key Issues, Feb 13, 1974, undated (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Queens Presidents' Council - 900, Dec 4, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Queens Presidents' Council - Extra Copies and Staff Notes, Mar 4, 1974-Apr 17, 1974, undated (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Queens Presidents' Council - Jackson Heights Region - Meeting Notes, Jun 3, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Queens Presidents' Council - Jackson Heights Region, Jun 3, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Queens Presidents' Council - Jackson Heights Region - 0131 and Leaders, Mar 7, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Queens Presidents' Council - Jackson Heights - 100, Jun 3, 19xx (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Queens Presidents' Council - Jackson Heights Region - 200, undated (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Queens Presidents' Council - Jackson Heights Region - 300, Jun 3, 19xx (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Queens Presidents' Council - Jackson Heights Region - 400, Jun 3, 19xx (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Queens Presidents' Council - Jackson Heights Region - 500, Jun 3, 19xx (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Queens Presidents' Council - Jackson Heights Region - 600, Jun 3, 1974, undated (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Queens Presidents' Council - Jackson Heights Region - 700, undated (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Queens Presidents' Council - Jackson Heights Region - 800, Jun 3, 19xx (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Queens Presidents' Council - Jackson Heights Region - 900, Jun 3, 19xx (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Queens Presidents' Council - Jackson Heights Region - Extra Sheets, undated (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Queens Presidents' Council - Student Papers, Feb 8, 1972-Jan 2, 1975, undated (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Parkchester Tenants Association, Oct 22, 1973-May 6, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Parkchester Tenants Association - Mailings and Clippings, Jul 1973, Nov 21, 1973, undated (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Parkchester Tenants Association - Student Papers, Clippings, Jan 3, 1973-May 23, 1974, undated (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Parkchester Tenants Association, Apr 20, 1973-May 6, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Parkchester Tenants Association - Meeting Notes, Oct 22, 1973-May 6, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Parkchester Tenants Association - 007 and Leaders, Apr 23, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Parkchester Tenants Association - 100: Ecology, Oct 22, 1973-Oct 24, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Parkchester Tenants Association - 200: Beginnings and History, Nov 1, 1973-May 6, 1974, undated (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Parkchester Tenants Association - 300: Structure and Finances, Apr 20, 1973[74], undated (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Parkchester Tenants Association - 400: Goals and Tactics, Oct 24, 1973-Apr 20, 1973[74],undated (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Parkchester Tenants Association - 500: Leaders and Key Personnel, May 6, 1974, undated (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Parkchester Tenants Association - 600 Membership and Mobilization, undated (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Parkchester Tenants Association - 700: The Observer and the Group, Oct 22, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Parkchester Tenants Association - 800 Movement and Key Issues, Apr 20, 1973[74] (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Parkchester Tenants Association - 900: Related Institutions, undated (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Riverdale Park Tenant Committee, Sep 23, 1973-Mar 20, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - Riverdale Park Tenants Association - United Riverdale Tenants Association, undated (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Riverdale Park Tenants Association - Meeting Notes, Sep 23, 1973-Feb 13, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - Riverdale Park Tenants Association, Sep 23, 1973-Feb 13, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - Riverdale Park Tenants Association - 015 and Leaders, Mar 20, 1974, undated (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - Riverdale Park Tenants Association - 100, Oct 19, 1973-Feb 6, 1974, undated (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - Riverdale Park Tenants Association - 200, Sep 23, 1973-Oct 19, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - Riverdale Park Tenants Association - 300, Sep 23, 1973, undated (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - Riverdale Park Tenants Association - 400, Sep 23, 1973-Feb 6, 1974, undated (Box 14, Folder 54)
  - Riverdale Park Tenants Association - 500, Sep 23, 1973-Feb 6, 1974, undated (Box 14, Folder 55)
  - Riverdale Park Tenants Association - 600, Oct 24, 1973, undated (Box 14, Folder 56)